The Soviet Union was saved by Ukrainians, Belarusians,
Советский Союз спасли украинцы белорусы
Kazakhs, and Tatars. All, all, all nations,
казахи Да татары Все всес всес народы
while the Russians stabbed our grandfathers in the back
пока русские нашим дедам нож в спину
with the Vlasov army and with
вставляли с власовское армией да с
these Cossack formations, yes, we
казачьими этими формированиями да мы
fought off the GIT. Look how many you
отбивали гит Посмотри сколько вот сейчас
googled now. How many Ukrainians
загугли Да сколько украинцев
died.
погибло
Hello,
Здравствуйте
Hello. What do you think? The US is a
Здравствуйте Как вы считаете США для
friend and enemy for Russia. Who will
России друг враг кто
take us forever? Cool. And when did you
брать на век Прикольно А когда вы
take us? On the horizon. Yeah. So it
побрал На горизонте Угу То есть
turns out that the US is not an
получается США - это не
imperialist power. No,
империалистическая держава Да нет
of course, what's interesting. Well, what about the
конечно что интересно ну а как же
US invasion of Iraq, Afghanistan,
вторжение США в Ирак в Афганистан в
Yugoslavia. There was the same leadership there
югославию там было руководство такое же
as in
как в Украине на
Ukraine. What does the people of Ukraine have to do with it? I
Украине народ тут при чём Поня
understand that freedom-loving people work. I understand that I
народ работать понял то я правильно
understand correctly that now Russia and the US are
понимаю что теперь Россия и США это уже
no longer enemies, they are
не враги это
partners. Of course, they
партнёры Конечно они адекватно
reason adequately. To develop
рассуждаю разрабатывать в этой в России
rare earth metals and aluminum in Russia. So it
там редкоземельные металлы алюминий То
turns out that Russia is becoming a raw materials
есть получается Россия стаёт сырьевым
appendage of the
придатком
West. Well, why
Запада Ну зачем так
say it like that. Well, that's how it turns out. Well, if that's
это говорить Ну так получается Ну если
not the point, we didn't
дело ведь не в этом мы ведь не это не
gather to kiss.  with them it is correct to
целоваться собрались с ними правильно
kiss like that Well Russia gives its
Так целоваться Ну Россия отдаёт свои
resources it turns out the United States was
ресурсы получается соединённым штатам
offered to develop in the Arctic they
предложили в Арктике разрабатывать
offered to extract that
предложили
is America does not let
добывать то есть Америка не пускает
Russia come to itself to extract something and Russia is
Россию к себе добывать что-то а Россия
just bowing to the Americans to
прямо ж кланяется американцам чтобы
let them into its market Well our
пустить их на свой рынок Ну у нас
technologies are not as
технологии не такие
developed I mean I mean I mean you are
развитые в смысле в смысле в смысле вы
not as developed as America of course
не такие развитые как Америка конечно
yeah yeah That is I understand that is you during the
угу То есть я понял то есть вы во время
Soviet Union the Soviet Union was the
Советского Союза Советский Союз был
world leader and now Russia is
лидером мировым А сейчас Россия
so far behind that it has become the
настолько отстала что стала срем
USA's [ __ ] What does the USA offer Just to dig up its
США Что предлагает США Просто выкапывать
own resources like that No you
у себя ресурсы так Нет вы так
reason as if you are a person from the
рассуждаете как будто вы Человек со
outside and how does Ukraine get to this in my opinion
стороны а как Украина к этому по-моему
everyone is already running with these yes with Ukraine no so
уже все бегут с этими да с Укра нет так
with Ukraine Everything is clear everything We have lost
с Украиной Всё понятно всё Мы проиграли
everyone is running And you it turns out I don't
все бегут А вы получается я вот не
understand Russia suffered so much to
понимаю Россия столько мучилась
prevent the hegemony of the USA yes And
чтобы не допустить гегемонию США да А
now it turns out it has fallen under the USA Just
теперь получается легла под США Просто
instantly no you misunderstood Russia has
моментально нет вы не так поняли Россия
already learned to
уже научилась
work with Western countries now for
работать с западными странами сейчас вот
example here they came We have a
например пришли У нас вот у меня
Renault car I personally have Yes and
автомобиль Renault вот у меня лично Да и
I like it I like it like this I like it like this
мне нравится он я такой это люблю по
forests to drive such a simple
лесам ездить такой простенький
car
автомобиль
D and everyone was knocked down and everyone drove with us and
D и всех валили и все ездили у нас и
taxis were this is what they are now
такси были это вот они сейчас к нам
asking us again
опять просятся
and they were told Sorry
а им сказали Извините
guys you treated us like pigs and
ребята вы с нами по свински поступили а
not Go to
не Шли бы вы
hell this is how they treat us now
лесом вот так вот относятся теперь уже
ours have learned yes maybe they will
наши научились да возможно они Америку и
accept America But not in such conditions As you for
примут Но не таких условиях Как вы
Christ's sake Take everything that only
Христа ради Возьмите всё что только нас
save us yes maybe there will be
спасите да возможно будет
compatibility in a
совмест сть
multipolar world now we are not talking
многополярном мире теперь речь не идёт
Russia just gave up in the race for
Россия просто сдалась в гонке
multipolarity and completely lay down under the
многополярность и полностью легла под
USA threw its friend China because
США кинула своего друга Китай потому что
uh Trump immediately said that for him China
ээ Трамп сразу сказал что для него Китай
is an enemy Yes and he is friends with Russia
- Это противник Да а с Россией он дружит
introduced duties on China That is, I
ввёл пошлины на Китай То есть я
understand correctly that the great
правильно понимаю что великий
Socialist China was
Социалистический Китай был предан
betrayed by Washington's puppets wrong
марионетками Вашингтона неправильно
Incorrect Russia will never go for
Неправильно Россия никогда не пойдёт на
betrayal of China neither So it has already gone
предательство Китая ни Так оно уже пошло
BC it it it began to be friends with the
ВС оно оно оно начало дружить с
imperialist monster with the USA everything the
империалистический монстром с США всё
Chinese also treat the
китайцы тоже хорошо относятся с
Americans well they have the largest
американцами у них самая большая
trade with the Chinese with the
торговля с китайцами с
Americans they even more so Let them
американцами они тем более Пусть они
even do something  they are at odds but they have the
даже и что-то враждуют но у них они
biggest turnover So we will
самый большой оборот Так что и мы будем
also be with America if something does
тоже с Америкой если что
not sell it is not
не продаст это не
Ukraine it is not she who She just would like If they
Украина это не она которая Она лишь бы
fed her she would run away quickly to the
Вот её бы накормили она убежала скорей
gang not so with Ukraine look with
банде не так с Украиной смотри с
Ukraine everything is clear yes to us to
Украиной всё понятно да
us what to the Americans what to the Europeans
нам нам что американцам что европейцам
what to the Turks We are like used to it
что туркам продастся Мы ж типа привыкли
yes yes but I do not understand Great Russia here
да да но я не пойму Великая Россия вот у
we have many politicians in Ukraine who
нас много политиков в Украине
say that we need to unite with
рассказывают что нужно объединяться с
Russia because Russia is a great
Россией потому что Россия великая
power only it will be able to repel
держава она только сможет дать отпор
America everything But here it turns out before our
Америке всё А тут получается на наших
eyes Russia simply caved in to
глазах Россия просто прогнулась под
America just like that well you know it just makes me
Америку просто так ну это аж прям знаете
ashamed for Russian
аж стыд берёт за российских
propagandists and politicians who
пропагандистов и политиков которые
simply ICE American politicians
просто ице американских политиков
imperialists bourgeois
империалистов буржуазных
Yes All our
Да Наши все
politicians are political scientists every day on
политики политологи вот каждый день по
TV they talk all the time Well yes
телевизору они всё время говорят Ну да
Now it seems like America has
Сейчас вроде бы Америка вот так курс
changed its course but no one says that here are
изменила но никто не говорит что вот вот
brothers here is all that now we are straight with the
братья вот всё такое сейчас мы прямо с
Americans We will kiss we do not
американцами Целоваться будем мы мы не
know what to expect from America now while
знаем что ждать от Америки сейчас пока
she speaks right  things and we
она говорит правильные вещи и мы
support these things what will happen next
поддерживаем эти вещи что дальше будет
We don't know like this if then
Мы не знаем вот так вот если то
Wait then are you friends or not friends Well
Подождите то вы друзья или не друзья Ну
I was joking then are you friends or not Well
я пошутил то всё-таки друзья или нет Ну
if this continues we
если дальше это будет продолжаться мы
may become friends then
может быть и станем друзьями то сейчас
who are you
кто вы
now we are still contracting
сейчас мы пока ещё договаривающиеся
parties nothing more if I
стороны больше ничего если
understood yes but at least they
так понял да но нас нас по крайней мере
don't humiliate us in the White
не унижают в Белом ме
House Yeah That's it
Угу Вот
And you still
так А Вы всё
dream you still dream you all want a sweet
мечите вы всё мечите всё хотите сладкой
life at someone else's expense
жизни за счёт кого-то
got it Yeah Yes yes yes now it's not like that look
понял Угу Да да да теперь не так смотри
with Ukraine it's clear Ukraine never
с Украиной понятно украино же никогда
existed at all Lenin invented it Like so
вообще не существовало её Ленин придумал
yes in 1917 yes yes yes yes Lenin
да в 917 году да дада да да Ленин
invented Ukraine created Well and we got
придумал Украину создал Да ну и мы
used to it we started running either to the Poles
привыкли мы начали бегать то к полякам
or to the Germans or to the French the
то к немцам то к французам
main thing is not with ROSI When did you run Yes
главно чтоб не с РОСИ Когда вы бегали Да
we always I just I just can't
мы всегда я просто я просто не могу
understand why Yes now comrade
понять зачем Да вот сейчас товарищ
Stalin is turning over in his grave just in his
Сталин переворачивается в гробу просто в
grave Yes to tell him that the Kremlin is
гробу Да чтобы ему сказать что Кремль
just kissing the Americans Yes he would I don't
просто целует американцев Да он бы не
know he would shoot  these
знаю он расстрелял бы этих
Putins don't care he doesn't
путино ниче он не
kiss right here you want to quarrel us with
целует прямо вот хотите нас поссорить с
America Americans so far at the moment they
Американ Американ пока на данный момент
said
говорили
lie This sa we
лье Это
have nothing against but nothing It is
са ничего против не имеем но ничего Пока
not known today you tomorrow there Trump
неизвестно сегодня вас завтра там Трамп
may say something bad about us in
может скажет про нас что-то плохое он же
my opinion he is going to introduce sanctions against
по-моему санкции собирается против
Russia this is all clear this and
России вводить это всё понятно это и
Poli we are still waiting for
Поли мы пока ждём
evil by disunity by the destruction of the Slavs
зла по разобщения по уничтожению славян
We remember this chessboard of
Мы помним вот этот шахматная доска
Zbigniew BZNS Yes all these plans for the
збигнева бзнс Да все вот эти планы по
collapse of the Soviet Union and now just
развала Советского Союза и теперь просто
some white gentleman from the
стоило какому-то белому господину из
oval
овального
office had to write something on Twitter that
кабинета написать что-то в Твиттере что
he uh wants to be friends with Putin and that's it and
он ээ хочет дружить с Путиным и всё и
Russia fell at the feet of America forgot all the
Россия легла к ногам Америки забыла все
humiliation of Russia and America forgot how
унижение России и америко забыла вот это
they mocked Bush with their legs
как ножками Буша они издевались
threw forgot how they
закидывали забыла как они Макдональдсы
set up their McDonalds forgot how they
свои Да настроили забыла как они
said that America is a hegemon
говорили что Америка гегемон
yes
да
look you somehow this is the very thing you
смотрите вы как-то это самое вы всё
always want something Well okay I missed the
время хотите что-то Ну ладно упустил я
point with these  Bush's legs Yes
момент вот этими ножками Буша Да
McDonald's they are asking to come to us again but you understand the
Макдональдса они опять к нам просятся но
place You understand that the
уже место-то ты понима Ты понимаешь что
Americans they are very cunning asking for
американцы они очень хитры просятся про
you asking in order to further give
ти прося для того чтоб дальше дать
their tentacles to Russia in order to rob the
своими щупальцами Россию чтоб ограбить
Russian people Yes take their resources
русский народ Да забирать ихние ресурсы
in order to make Russia an appendage of the
чтобы сделать снова Россию придатком
West again it's the same as under Yeltsin the entire
Запада это же как при ельцине весь
sixth floor of the White House in Moscow was
шестой этаж Белого дома да в Москве был
planted by American emissaries you
посажен американскими эмиссара вы же
know It's true
знаете Это правда
so listen here is a Ukrainian flag behind you
так послушайте вот за вами украинский
Yes behind us you are sitting in such a way
Да за ми вы сидите в такой
all the time telling What
всё время рассказываете Какие
Americans So why are you sitting with this
американцы Так чего же вы сидите с этим
Ukrainian flag why are you telling me all this You say
украинским флагом вы для чего это мне
Look so that I would tell you something
всё Говорите Смотрите для того чтобы я
bad about
вам высказал что-то такое нехорошее про
America and you posted something somewhere or something So did
Америку а вы что-то куда-то там выложили
you have your own head when you
ли у вас свои своя голова была когда вы
went with America Well I understand you are cunning
сходили с америко Ну я понял вы хитры
Okay I admit you are me Chile I
Ладно я признаюсь вы меня Чили я сюда
came here specifically to
вышел специально для того чтобы
talk to the Russians write down how
поговорить с россиянами записать как они
badly they think about America translate it into
плохо думают об Америке перевести это на
English and send  Donald
английский язык и прислать дональду
Trump to
трампу чтобы это
show this to CNN I wanted this Yes because
показали CNN я этого хотел Да потому что
I had only this plan How to
у меня был только вот такой план Как
open the eyes of Americans to the fact that
открыть глаза американцам на то что
Russians still think badly of them Well
россияне всё-таки думают о них плохо Ну
you exposed me yes You are very much you are
вы меня раскрыли да Вы очень вы такой
this very thing confessed everything well just everything well
это самое сознались всё ну прям всё ну
where can I go I had nowhere to
куда уже мне мне уже некуда было
talk you drove me into a corner and
говорить вы меня в угол забили и
had to confess Well it was already obvious
пришлось признаться Ну уже очевидно было
yes you seem Now let out a tear
да вы похоже Сейчас слезу Выпустите
right I am just like that It's a pity yes I was thinking
прямо я прямо вот Жалко да это я думал
how to save Ukraine I think That's it Well there
как спасти Украину думаю Вот Вот Ну вот
is now some old man I'll find and write it down
есть сейчас какого-то деда найду запишу
And you are not such a simpleton as you seem well
А вы не такой простак как кажетесь ну
tell me and you and you how do you
скажите а вы а вы вы-то как сейчас
feel about America now about America Yes
относитесь к Америке к Америке Да
America is now captured by the sect Trump
Америка сейчас захвачена сектой трам
Yes it's very much a
Да это очень такая
neo-fascism let's
неофашизм
just say normally perceived
просто скажем нормально воспринимал вот
this neo-Nazi Wow channel So the person
эту неонацист Вах канали Так что человек
in the leadership essentially yes of the United
в руководстве по сути да Соединённых
States of America Yes throws off the Hitler
Штатов Америки Да скидывает гитлеровское
salute Well it's just I don't know it's a
приветствие Ну это просто я не знаю это
shame grandfathers our grandfathers who fought with
позор деды наши деды которые воевали с
Hitler are just spinning in  gorbach
Гитлером просто вертятся в горбах
comrade Stalin I just don't know He already
товарищ Сталин просто не знаю Он уже
wants to get up and shoot everyone No you
хочет встать и Расстрелять всех Нет вы
What right do you have to say our grandfathers Here are our grandfathers My grandfather
Какое имеете право сказать наши деды Вот
My grandfather My grandfather Hero of the
наши деды Мой дед Мой дед Мой дед Герой
Soviet Union yes yes that's it and
Советского Союза да да вот оно а ваши
yours yours yes our grandfathers Ukrainian Yes they fought
ваши да наши деды украинские Да воевали
And the most killed were Ukrainians in
И само больше погибших - это украинцы во
World War II And your grandfathers were a
Второй мировой войне А ваши деды были
million people in the Vlasov army
миллион человек во власовское армии
Russian liberation army
русская освободительная армия
collaborators still another another up to a
коллаборационисты ещё ещё ещё до
million people in the ROVS program Cossack
миллиона человек в проги ровс казачьих
troops were all over the Don and Kuban Yes
войсках были весь Дон и Кубань Да вот
these all Krasnovs Generals Krasnovs yes that
эти все красновы Генералы красновы да то
is Russia in Russia
есть России в России
Russians rushed very hard We
русские очень сильно кинулись Мы же это
remember this Yes they dreamed of the
помним Да они ж мечтали о
White Guard movement and it
белогвардейского движении а оно
completely supported Hitler Yes this is
полностью поддержало Гитлера Да вот это
all counterrevolution
контрреволюция вся
and no stop and Hitler was beaten off Yes the Soviet
и нет стоп и Гитлера отбили Да Советский
Union was saved by Ukrainians Belarusians Kazakhs Yes
Союз спасли украинцы белорусы казахи Да
Tatars all-all all the peoples while the Russians
татары все-все всес народы пока русские
stabbed our grandfathers in the back with the
нашим дедам нож в спину вставляли с
Vlasov army and with these Cossack
власовское армии да с казачьими этими
formations yes we  they fought off the GIT
формированиями да мы отбивали гит
Look how many googled how many
Посмотри сколько загугли сколько
Ukrainians died the most Ukrainians
украинцев погибло само больше украинцев
died Kazakhs died and Russians the
погибло казахи погибли а русские само
most there were traitors to the Motherland among the
больше было предателей Родины среди
Russians so here is the answer how it turns
русских так можно такой вот ответ како
out in the Vlasov army 75% were
оказывается во власко армии 75% было
Ukrainians I wonder if the Vlasov
украинцев интересно если власовская
army was formed on the territory of the RSFSR
армия формировалась на территории РСФСР
how did it happen that there could be
как так получилось что там может быть
70% Ukrainians there
70% украинцев
Listen where did you get the idea that on the
Послушайте Вы с чего взяли что на
territory of the RSFSR on the territory of the RSR
территории РСФСР на территории РСР
Comrade Stalin clearly ruled his
товарищ Сталин руководил чётко своей
country there could not have been
страной там не могло быть
anyone there look on the territory of the RSFSR we
никого смотрите на территории РСФСР мы
know on the territory of the Bryansk Kursk
знаем на территории Брянской Курской
region the so-called
области была организована так называемая
Lokot Republic was organized a Nazi
локотская республика нацистское
state entity which
государственное образование которые
simply not only even fought for Hitler
просто не просто даже воевали за Гитлера
they proclaimed Yes their state
они провозгласили Да своё ээ государство
Lokot Republic declared the Soviet
локотской Республику объявили Советский
Union to the occupiers Yes and the population of this
Союз оккупантам Да и население вот этой
Bryansk region to Kursk who were
Брянской области до Курской которые
part of this
входили в эту
Lokot to the Germans faithfully and truly Yes and
локотской немцам верой и правдой Да а
simply uh participated in the formation of
просто ээ участвовали в формировани
such anti-Soviet movements Well we  we
антисоветских таких движений Ну мы же
know this i am still a person who was
это знаем мы я ещё человек который 0
born in the first year yes i was still
первого года рождения Да я ещё в
studying in the Soviet Union at the beginning and we
Советском Союзе учился в начале и мы это
went through all this they told us about all
всё проходили нам рассказывали про все
these Russian collaborators and why why yes
эти коллаборационистов русских и почему
just comrade Stalin yes
почему Да как раз товарищ Сталин Да
he hates all these Russian
он так вот этих всех русских
collaborators and more than that
коллаборационистов ненавидит и больше
look now yes that in
того Посмотрите сейчас Да что у нас в
Russia we have the Vlasov flag tricolor
России имеется власовский флаг Триколор
listen further wait still I am telling
послушайте дальше Подождите ещ
fortunes then about the Vlasov army if
ворожу значит по власовское армии если
you open the memoirs of the General of the
вы откроете Мемуары Генерала армии
UPA army Taras
упа Тараса
Borovets who wrote in seventy-
боровца который написал в семьдесят
ninth or eighty-first year in
девятом или восемьдесят первом году в
Canada he escaped to Canada he was a
Канаде Он сбежал в Канаде он был
general of the UPA so in his
генералом упа так вот он в своих
memoirs he writes that I am Agirova and about
мемуарах пишет что я агирова та по
concentration camps and with all this therefore formed the
концлагеря и этим всем значит формировал
army of Vlasovites and he said he
армию власовцев и он сказал он там
wrote there this direct participant
написал это непосредственный участник
that more than 70% in the Vlasov army were
что более 70% в армии Власова было
Ukrainians no no look what again
украинцев нет нет смотри что ещё раз нет
no now look not a single historian will
вот сейчас смотрите ни один историк
tell you the Vlasov army
такой вам не скажет власовская армия на
was 95% ethnic  Russians
95% состояла из этнических русских
other nationalities there are no more than
остальные национальности там не больше
5% this is a fact in this is a historical fact
5% это факт в это исторический факт
historical
исторический
fact Okay, let me read it now
факт Хорошо давайте сейчас прочитаю
so I read here is the ethnic composition of
так так читаю вот этнический состав
Vlasov's army 95.37
армии Власова 95,37
Well, here are the official data this is a report so
Ну вот официальные данные это отчёт так
Moscow State University
Московский государственный университет
yes the history department listen I
да кафедра истории послушайте я вам
gave you an example You can open this
привёл пример Вы можете открыть эту
book Taras
книгу Тарас
Borovets I opened Moscow
Боровец Я открыл Московский
State University the
государственный университет кафедра
history department the history department of Moscow
истории кафедра истории Московского
State University look
Государственного университета смотрите
here orders the Order of the Red Banner and the
вот тут ордена ордена Красного Знамени и
Order of Lenin the history department to the
ордена Ленина кафедра истории
Russian population to the Russian population
русскому населению по-русскому населению
I tell you comrade Stalin who
я вам до говорю товарищ Сталин который
went through all this and won the Second World
прошёл это всё и выиграл вторую мировую
War not Russian mind you Not Russian he is
Войну не русский заметьте Не русский он
not Russian and Vlasov was a traitor
не русский а Власов был предатель
Russian listen he is not Russian but he
русский послушайте он не русский но он
said the main
сказал главный
winner in the Great Patriotic War
победитель в Великой Отечественной войне
is the Russian people did not say he is
является русский народ не говорил он
like that no he said the Soviet people
такой нет он говорил Советский народ
Check Check the advice so not Soviet
Проверяй Проверь совет так не советский
but Russian Let's now exactly the Russian
а русский Давай сейчас именно русский
people
народ
so from the speech from the speech of comrade Stalin at the
так из речи из речи товарища Сталина на
congress of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union the main winner in the Great
съезде КПС главным победителем в Великой
Patriotic War is the Soviet
Отечественной войне является Советский
people and  his socialist
народ и его социалистическое
government that's how it was said no It's
правительство вот как сказано нет Это
yours look find find It's your
ваши посмотри найди найди Это ваши
propagandists who are now saying that the Russian
пропагандисты сейчас говорят что русский
people in the Soviet Union there was no
народ в Советском Союзе не было
division between Russians and non-Russians were all
разделения русские и нерусские были все
Soviet yesyes yes the main hardships
советские дадада именно основные тяготы
so here's what else look now
так вот дальше ещё ем смотри теперь
tell me yes tell me such a simple
скажи мне да скажи мне такую простую
thing if now your president of the
вещь если сейчас у вас президент
Russian Federation Vladimir Putin
Российской Федерации Владимир Путин
considers
считает
his favorite philosopher
своим любимым философом
Ilyin who was a real supporter of
Ильина который реально был сторонником
fascism Yes Ilyin wears flowers Buried in
фашизма Да носит цветы Ильин Похоронен в
Russia now perep moreover you
России сейчас перепон более того у вас
revere such an ideologist of Nazism Lev
почитается такой идеолог нацизма Лёв
by the way when the Germans were standing near
между прочим когда немцы стояли под
Moscow Yes Shmelev wrote to Ilyin in a letter
Москвой Да Шмелёв писал ильину в письме
Yes what finally this
Да что вот наконец-то это этих
red bubble
краснопузырник
what to you Ilyin Putin Yes I honestly don't
что тебе Ильин Путин Да я этого честно
know much about this so here yes
говоря не больно зна так вот да вот
let's find out now Why Yes come on come on
давай сейчас узнаем Почему Да давай
why Putin supports the Nazi
давай почему Путин поддерживает нациста
Ilin
Илина
Putin now a
Путин сейчас
second so
секун так
for what Why are you in such a hurry what are you
за что Да что ты все торопишься что ты
now a second now we are
сейчас секундочку сейчас мы
interested come on Ilin Putin look at your
интересно давай Илин Путин посмотри
favorite philosopher  respects Ilin
нку любимый фило тин уважает Илина
so let's
так
see which I
посмотрим которы
think now I quote the statement of this
думаю сечас цитирую высказывание это
philosopher so funny so many of
философа так бавно такого
us politicians
большо мы политиков
write that Ilin was a fascist but
некоторые пишут что Илин был фашистом но
this is not true the philosopher never
это не правда философ никогда не
supported the Nazi and especially
поддерживал нацистскую а тем более
fascist ideologists
фашистскую идеологи
Yes at first even welcomed his rise
Да сначала даже приветствовал его приход
to power but quickly became disillusioned with the
к власти но быстро разочаровался в
dictatorship and the policies produced in
диктатуре и производимой политики в
moved to Switzerland that is Nilina
переехал в Швейцарию то есть нилина
quoted
цитировал
Putin at that time So they lived
Путин врем Так жили
worked with that
работали с
is everyone first goes along the path of
то есть каж сначала идут по пути
development reach heights and then
развития достигают высот а потом
regression decline begins I think that
начинается регресс упадок я счита что
if disputes arise around these ideas
если вокруг идей этих возникает
whoever loves Russia should wish
споры кто любит Россию тот должен желать
for it Freedom first of all freedom for
для неё Свободы прежде всего свободы для
Russia itself e international independent freedom
самой России е международ незави имо
for
свобо для
Hello grandpa come on go back to the family Come on
Алло дед давай возвращайся в семью Давай
you mumble something there look that is
ты что-то там бубнишь смотри то есть
Ilin was a fascist he even has
Ильин был фашистом у него даже есть
such a monograph on Russian fascism
такое это монография о русском фашизме
where he talked about how it would be good
где он рассказывал как это будет хорошо
for
для
Russia here is Ilin's statement in this
России вот высказывание Илина в это
right in the photo Russia has no sincere people in the world
прямо на фотографии у России нет в мире
well-wishers the Russian people
искренних доброжелателей русский народ
can only hope for God and themselves
может надеяться только на Бога и на себя
so write Ilyin is a fascist write and you will have a
вот напиши Ильин фашист напиши и тебе
bunch Here everything has been said
куча будет Вот здесь сказано все сказано
he even welcomed at first to this
он даже приветствовал сначала вык этому
Yes he he Look he was for Benito
Да он он Смотри он был за бенита
Mussolini for Hitler was yes yes yes yes come on come on they
Муссолини за Гитлера был да да да да
write look some write he
давай вот пишут смотрите некоторые пишут
was a fascist but this is not true the philosopher
н был фашистом но это неправда философ
never supported the Nazi and even
никогда не поддерживал нацистскую а тем
more so a fascist no lie Take Take right now right
более фашист нет брехня Возьми Возьми
now I am
вот прямо сейчас прямо сейчас я тебе
telling you right now dial Ilyin about Russian
говорю вот сразу набери Илин о русском
fascism and it will open the text for you right here this is
фашизме и тебе откроет прям текст его
how he supported Come on where are you
вот это как он поддерживал Давай куда
running away to, grandfather Well grandfather grandfather grandfather don't hang out
дед убегаешь Ну дед дед дед не Зависай
Oh damn you grandfather
Ах ты блин Дед
and grandfather hung up the [ __ ] got
а дед зави
burned
сюка подгорел
ran away how I love it when
убежал как я люблю это когда говорит
our grandfathers say they are like that with such contempt And what do
наши деды они такие с таким презрением А
your grandfathers have to do with it Yes the Russians have such a
ваши деды причём Да у Россиян такая
thing that in the Second
значит какая-то штука что во Второй
World War it means their grandfathers were Russians who
мировой войне значит ихние деды русские
fought against Hitler And
там воевали против Гитлера А все
all the other grandfathers were in short  collaborators
остальные деды короче были коллаборанты
like for this for Hitler guys no no
типа за это за Гитлера ребятки нет нет
If you look yes then in Ukraine yes The
Если Вы посмотрите да то в Украине да
largest number of people killed in
Самое большое количество погибших во
World War II in the USSR And in
Второй мировой войне жителей СССР А в
Russia the largest number of
России самое большое количество
collaborators all this Russian
коллаборантов вся вот эта русская
Liberation Army Yes Vlasov all
освободительная армия Да Власова все вот
these Cossack formations of the Wehrmacht yes yes
эти казачьи формирования Вермахта да
so let's go subscribe to my telegram
да так поехали подпишись на мий телеграм
right now axis vin and
прямо зараз ось вин а
popk this is very and very lively YouTube Zaga
попк це дуже и дуже ливо YouTube Зага
us through scarg ORV in your ban and very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твий бан и дуже
many videos I do not show to people at times I do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams That is why
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we Mali operational links ppi
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок ппи
right now and while there in telegram okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
video there is also interesting and useful information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we are obliged to you three permanent
и мы повинни з вами трима постийний
operational links
оперативный звязок
independently in that chi will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава Украине подпишись